Resume

Personal details

Name Nika Nishnianidze

Email address nika.nishnianidze.10@gmail.com

Phone number +995 571087098

Address Gldani, 4 M/D, 0167 Tbilisi

Date of birth April 20, 1998

Gender Male

Website yolosopher.site



Profile

I am a Frontend Developer with a background in Business Management. I have several years of experience in frontend development and possess a strong skillset that includes **Git/Github/Gitlab**, **HTML5**, **CSS/SASS**, **Typescript/Javascript/JQuery**, **API/CRUD**, **SocketIO/Websockets**, **MongoDB/Mongoose/Firebase**,

PostgreSQL/MySQL, NodeJS/ExpressJS/NestJS, ReactJS/NextJS, Webpack/Gulp/Vite, Docker/Docker Compose/Deployment, and Jest for unit-testing. I am passionate about creating user-friendly interfaces and am always eager to learn and adapt to new technologies in the ever-evolving world of web development.

Education

Sep 2018 - Jun 2021 Business Management

Ilia State University, Tbilisi

Sep 2016 - May 2018 Philosophy

Ilia State University, Tbilisi

After studying philosophy for two years, I developed an interest in economics and

switched faculties.

Employment

Aug 2021 - May 2023 Frontend Developer

Lime Consulting, Ukraine, Kyiv (Remote)

This job was also a fantastic experience where I tackled new challenges, working

on the frontend of various gambling websites.

Apr 2020 - Aug 2021 Frontend Developer

Smartweb, Tbilisi

My first job was a great learning experience where I worked on various projects

and gained a lot of hands-on experience in frontend development.

May 2022 - Present Fullstack Developer

Freelance, Georgia, Tbilisi + Remote

Certificates

Feb 2020 **Smart Academy - Front-End Development Course**

A(90+ out of 100)

Nov 2021 **Smart Academy - ReactJS Course**

A(90+ out of 100)

Skills

Git/Github/Gitlab Excellent

HTML5, CSS/SASS Excellent

Typescript/Javascript/JQuery Excellent

API/CRUD Excellent

SocketIO/Websockets Excellent

MongoDB/Mongoose/Firebase Excellent

NodeJS/ExpressJS/NestJS Very good

ReactJS/NextJS Very good

Webpack/Gulp/Vite Very good

PostgreSQL/MySQL Good

Compose/Deployment

Moderate

Jest

Languages

Docker/Docker

Georgian Fluent

English Very good

Qualities

- Quick learner, Smart
- Exemplary sense of accountability
- Good sense of humor, Cheerful, Team worker
- Determined and Goal-oriented
- Composed and Self-assured